you say 60% of the globe's resources are
ты говоришь 60% земного шарика ресурсов
in Russia, but why then do you
в России а почему ты ж тогда в такой
live worse than a poor country in such a resource-rich country
богатой ресурсами стране живёшь хуже чем
[laughter]
[смех]
Great Good afternoon, look I'm with the
Здорово Добрый день вот смотрите Я у
people I'm healthy those with the people I wish you
людей Здоров те у людей здоровья тебе
good health Happy belated Victory Day to you
крепкого с прошедшим днём Победы тебя
dear Okay I'm with
дорогой Окей я у людей из России
I'm asking people from Russia how do you feel about the war in
спрашиваю как вы относитесь к войне в
Ukraine well not completely Understandable To be
Украине ну не до конца Понятно Если
honest And so God forbid that there
честно А так-то дай Бог чтобы войны
is no war at all Well, now it is
вообще не было Ну а вот она сейчас есть
What do you think your country
Как вы считаете правильно ваша страна
did right by attacking Ukraine or
сдела что напала на Украину или
wrong Who Who  we are such ordinary
неправильно Кто Кто мы такие обычные
serfs
холопы
but do you live in the principality of Moscow
тно вы в княжестве живёте в Московском
or in the Russian
или в Российской
Federation Why are we in the Russian Federation
Федерации Зачем в Российской Федерации
but I simply do not doubt the sanity of my
находимся но просто я в здравость своего
leader Vladimir Vladimirovich Putin
лидера Владимира Владимировича Путина не
if he does something he
сомневаюсь если что-то он делает он
does it all for a reason and he
делает это всё не просто так и ему уж
knows better More  I repeat, who am I
видней Ещё раз повторюсь кто я такой
to talk about how he acts?
чтобы рассуждать о том как действует он
We still won’t understand it. Well,
мы всё равно это не поймём хорошо Ну
look, you have a
смотри э у тебя есть паспорт гражданина
Russian passport.  You are not a subject of the Federation You are a
Российской Федерации ты не подданный Ты
citizen so of course everything is correct And
гражданин так конечно всё правильно А в
what is the essence of a
чём суть
citizen in civic duty probably
гражданина в гражданском долге наверное
and in rights and obligations so that is
и в правах и обязательствах так то есть
you have the right and some rights and
у вас есть право и и права и
obligations and you choose
обязательства какие-то и вы избирает
your ruler prince So you are not
своего правителя князя Так вы же не
slaves  which Yes the prince said Here you are
холопы которые Да князь сказал Вот вы
my serfs And you elected him and he
мои холопы А вы избрали его и он от
acts on your behalf
вашего имени действует
so Everything is correct then it means you
так Всё правильно то значит вы несёте
also bear some share of
тоже получается какую-то долю
responsibility for his actions You
ответственности за его действия Вы же
authorized him well how can I
уполномочить ну к вам как могу
address you What is your
обращаться Вас как
name as a citizen  want to contact
зовут как гражданин хотите обратиться
or as a
или как
serf if as a
холоп если как
citizen
гражданин
residents of Zhdan
жители Ждан
Stvore Andrey my name is Eduard in general
створе Андрей меня Эдуард зовут вцелом
here [ __ ] you know how I will tell you In general
вот сри знаешь как тебе скажу В целом
of course it is unpleasant that Well really here
конечно неприятно то что Ну реально вот
Three brothers Three brothers Kievan
Три брата Три брата Киевская
Rus Nizhny
Русь Нижне
Novgorod book Read it please this is
новгоро книга Прочитай её пожалуйста это
when the Baptism of Rus began when else  there
когда Крещение Руси началось когда ещё
was Kievan Rus so What three brothers
была Киевская Русь так Какие три брата
What three brothers Kievan Rus Novgorod and the
Какие три брата кивская Русь Новгород и
third brother who the hell I don't remember
третий брат кто блин не помню
damn Andryukh Look look here in a few
блин Андрюх Вот смотри смотри вот в двух
words I'll explain to you The matter  not that
словах тебе объясню Дело не в том то что
I remember now I don't remember Yes, it's just that
я сейчас помню не помню Да вот просто
initially you I suppose against the background of the flag of
изначально ты я так полагаю на фоне флаг
our Ukrainian brothers you that is for
наших братьев украинцев ты то есть за
Ukraine you rule from this Rhone
Украину ты с этой Роны
I see Look initially
прави Понятно Вот смотри изначально
you these devils Demons Yes the
вас вот эти вот дьяволы Демоны Да
United States of America with panto
Соединённые Штаты Америки с панто
shot down Or maybe not
сбили А может и нет
you were shot down there too Well that is to say
вас там сбил тоже Ну то есть ему там
Europe I don't know what promised you its interests
Европа не знаю что обещала свои интересы
you welcomed here look Andryukh
вам приветствовал вот смотри Андрюх
just a trick question Bandera is a hero
просто Вопрос на засыпку Бандера герой
for you yes Stepan Andreevich Bandera Yes a
для тебя да Степан Андреевич Бандера Да
hero And why is he a hero what heroic thing
герой А почему герой он что геройского
did he do because he  fought for the will of
сделал потому что он боролся за Волю
Ukraine so that it would be a free
Украины за то чтобы она была свободным
state or something like that
государством се что ли А
Wait, don't wait, but how did he
подожди не подожди а каким образом он
fight Bandera Who was he like that in
боролся Бандера Кто он был вот такой
general, you all talk about Bandera
вообще вот у вас все говорят про бандеру
who he was a man, a human being, he is not Well, in
кем он был человек человеко он нет Ну в
principle, I know that  that this A is a bandit and that
принципе я знаю то что этот А бандюган и
something Well, yes, yes, yes, yes, the bandit
то что то Ну вот дада да слу слу бандюк
robbed, really killed people, strengthened his power,
грабил реально убивал людей свою власть
thereby you can name
укреплял тем самым можете назвать
how many people Bandera killed and who
сколько людей убил Бандера и кого вот
can Well, where do I get it from?  34 years old Andryukh
может Ну откуда мне Мне 34 года Андрюх
where can I
откуда могу
Well where can I what can I push away from
Ну откуда что я могу я отталкиваю от
what is written in books What
того что пишут в книгах Что
they say they say how many people
говорят говорят сколько людей убил
Bandera killed how many one 10 million here is
Бандера сколько одного 10 миллион вот
Stalin I know he killed millions but he is some kind of
Сталин Я знаю миллионы убил но он что-то
hero Hero not a hero hardly something he
герой Герой не герой навряд ли что-то он
hero It seems to me that Stalin's repressions are
герой Мне кажется сталинские репрессии у
still condemned here outside so that you
нас до сих пор осуждаются вне чтоб ты
understand
понима
very much Moscow loves powerful leaders
ли очень Мос любят мощных лидеров
who are like princes so that they
которые вот которые князь чтоб там сразу
are not citizens but cold ones. Understand Yes, it's just that serfs don't like
были Поня Да просто холопы не любят
democratic leaders who
демократических лидеров вот которые
shake their hands, they are loved Yes A
трясёт рукой вот их любят Да А вы сами с
What region of
какого региона
Russia are you from Tatarstan Well, the Republic of
России Татарстана Ну Республика
Tatarstan, and are you Tatars or Russians,
Татарстан о а вы сами татары или русские
who are you Well, I am a Tatar too, my comrades are
кто вы Ну я татарин тоже у меня товари
Tatars, Tatars, and you are Tatars, you
татари татары так а и вы мне татары
are telling me about the Three Brothers, there is
рассказываете про Три брата там Киевская
some kind of Kievan Rus, wait, wait, guys,
Русь какая-то подождите подождите ребята
you are the Muscovite Kingdom  in which in the 10th or in
вас Московское царство в каком в X или в
which century or in the 15th
каком веке или в XV
century in which century Kazan was captured 14
веке в каком веке Казань захватили 14
sheets of Ivan the Terrible's second now
листа секунду Ивана Грозного сейчас
you remember yes  Andryukh well when they captured I
вспоминаешь да Андрюх ну когда захвати я
don't know who's for I know that Kazan was
не знаю кто за Я знаю что Казань
captured they slaughtered a bunch of Tatars and so this is
захватили вырезали кучу татар так и вот
it
это это
Ivan the Terrible was going to Kazan
шл Иван Грозный на Казань
When Ivan the Terrible when he was going to Kazan
Когда Иван Грозный когда на Казань шл
seriously I don't know I know I can
вот серьёзно не знаю Я знаю могу
tell So that Ivan the Terrible would know for the future  with
рассказать Чтобы знал на будущее ёл Иван
his countless hordes
Грозный со своим не сметным по полчище
to Kazan,
на Казань то
that is, in the
есть в
rivers Kama and Volga, many Tatars were drowned
реках Камы и Волги много татар было утоп
who did not agree to be baptized,
тех кто не соглашались креститься
so his last refuge was on the
вот последнее его пристанище было на
lands of Sviyazhsk. Well, before the campaign against
землях Свияжска Ну перед походом на
Kazan, as it were, the Cursed Land. The land is
Казань как бы Проклятая земя Земля вот
now considered fresh. Well, that there is a
сейчас свеж считается Ну то что там
swamp there.  Well, and in fact, a lot of people
болото Ну и там на самом деле народа
died there, so-and-so And so if you take any history
погибло так-то А так если любую историю
Yes, Andryukh, to be honest,
брать Да Андрюх вот если честно на
throughout the entire history that was
протяжении вот всей истории что вот
written Yes, there
писалось Да людьми там человечества
was literally no war between people there for humanity for 100-something
войны не было буквально 100 с чем-то
days No, well, I  that's not what I'm talking about, look
дней Не ну я я не про то я вот смотри о
what I'm talking about, you yourself are an ethnic Tatar. So
чём я вот ты сам этнический татарин Так
you were once, your ancestors were
ты когда-то был вот твои предки были
conquered, and now you are to me  you say
завоёваны так и сейчас ты мне говоришь
that there is America or there is Bandera or
что там Америка или там Бандера какой-то
something there who set the Ukrainians against the
что-то там украинцев настроил против
Russians. My brain is just exploding, I
русс У меня просто мозг взрывается я
understand if you were some Russian
понимаю если бы ты был каким-то русским
from Moscow and this is a Russian name or what. Well,
с Москвы а это русское имя или какое Ну
Andrey. In Ukrainian, it's Andrey in-  Russian
Андрей Это по-украински Андрей по-русски
And in general, what is Andrey's name? Well,
А вообще Андрей это какое имя Ну
Greek, Greek, are you Greek or something? There are
греческое греческое ты грек что ли
no countries. Look, look, Andrei is
Нет стран смотри смотри Андр эрд же тоже
not a European either. Let's go in now. God forbid you
не европеец прам зайдём сечас Не дай Бог
call us names. We
обзываться
want a wall from you. I just want to
стену хотим от вас вот я просто хочу
figure it out. Look, why, why do
разобраться смотри а вот зачем а зачем
we need it?  we don't understand here
вот нам вот непонятно нам вот
ho What's the joke then we we really here
хо Что за прикол то мы мы-то реально вот
knows Here to us in Bugulma here I am in
знает Вот к нам в Бугульма вот я в
Tatarstan in
Татарстане в
Bugulma roughly speaking a month ago Yes on
Бугульме грубо говоря месяц назад Да в
Saturday 90 refugees from Ukraine arrived to
субботу приехало 90 беженцев с украины к
us in Bugulma arrived You can't
нам в бугульму приехала Ты не
imagine They are here Well  roughly speaking, I
представляешь Им тут Ну грубо говоря да
almost lick what the unfortunate
чуть ли не облизываю то что несчастные
people have seen. What is war, as it were? Well, you
люди застали Что такое война как бы Ну
understand. And  these refugees are all over the country now
понимаешь И это же по всей стране сейчас
look Wait where did
эти беженцы смотри Подожди от откуда
these refugees come from why did they
взялись эти беженцы из-за чего они
start
начали
running away Andryukh because your
убегать Андрюх из-за того что твоя
country brought troops here and chased
страна притащила сюда войска и погоняла
them out of their homes So why why
их из своих домов Так а почему а почему
look our country started unleashing a
смотри наша страна начала развязала
war  Let it be so
войну Пусть будет так
And you know very well that our intelligence
А у нас ты прекрасно знаешь разведка
works very well
работает очень хорошо
Yeah, when did you start building these
Угу когда вы начали строить Вот эти
laboratories and start pushing out these missile systems,
лаборатории и начали вот эти комплексы
this is on our border
шмат выдвигать так это на нашей границе
For what What laboratories What
Для чего Какие лаборатории Какие
laboratories were on your borders I
лаборатории были на ваших границах я
chemical chemically for the first time this
химические химически первый раз это
I hear And where did they stand
слышу А где они стояли
Biden's SN
СН байдена
Directly recorded how to
Непосредственно зафиксирован как
say correctly in that he has
правильно сказать в том то что он имеет
involvement in this to all And he what
причастность к этому ко всему А он что
he Some kind of chemist what was he doing there
он Химик какой-то что он там делал сын
Biden's son Well why did he control already Andryukh
байдена Ну зачем контролировал уж Андрюх
Where where In Kharkov Mariupol where is this
Где где В Харькове Мариуполе где это
laboratory  was I want to know I'll say
лаборатория была Я хочу узнать скажу вот
now look now I'm pushing away
сейчас смотри сейчас отталкиваю
cut And if they deceive imagine
отре А если они обманут представляешь
this is not Biden's son This was Peskov's daughter
это не сын байдена Это дочка Пескова
They deceived
Они обманули
Or maybe it is that they deceived and Peskov
А может быть такое что обманули а Песков
paid money to the media so that they wouldn't say that
заплатил деньги СМИ чтобы не сказали что
it was
это сын
Biden's son Andrey Well, anything is possible, there are
байдена Андрю ну всякое может быть слов
no words You understand this perfectly well
нет Вот это сам же прекрасно понимаешь
We look I don't know what you do for a living
мы вот смотри я не знаю кем ты работаешь
Yes, a
да
programmer Programmer
программист программист
Yes, the head of the base I am  I recently
Да начальник базы Я вот недавно домой
came home to my family to my relatives to my family to my wife
приехал к своим к родным к семье К жене
there and yes to the kids and now I'm
там да ну к детям и вот сейчас вот
enjoying myself a little and in general Well there I was
кайфую маленько и в целом Ну там-то был
in the north it was completely incomprehensible Look I'm
на севере вообще было непонятно Смотри я
not talking about this not about the north it's all lyrics
не про это не про север это всё лирика
Look your you  you say refugees and we
Вот смотри ваша ты говоришь беженцы и мы
accept them there you started a war drove
там их принимаем вы начали войну выгнали
people out bombed their houses brought them
людей разбомбили ихние дома привезли их
to Russia and now you say we
в Россию и теперь говорите вот мы для
are doing good for them Maybe it is easier to remove your
них делаем добро Может проще убрать свои
troops from Ukraine
войска с Украины
maybe I won't tell you for sure But
может быть не скажу тебе точно Но тем не
nevertheless Look they bombed the damage yes yes
менее Смотри дамага разбомбили да да да
yes Well, how? If your military
Ну а как Если ваши военные под этими
is hiding under these houses and placing these or those
домами прячутся размещают те или иные
installations, they are
установки они
not afraid of placing installations in cemeteries, I
не им не стрёмно на кладбищах размещать
understand, here now  bone turn oh well
понима тут сейчас разворот кости а ну
say this thing Russian troops are
скажи такую вещь русские войска вот
now in occupied Kherson They are
сейчас в оккупированном Херсоне Они же
standing in Kherson in the city it's
стоят в Херсоне в городе
true they were standing Yes in occupied Bucha
правда стояли Да в оккупированной буче
They were standing in the city they were standing in
Они же стояли в городе стояли в
Borodyanka Russian troops were standing in our
бородянке стояли русские войска в нашем
city like that Why can Russian troops
городе стояли так Почему русские войска
stand in  city ​​and our troops
можно им стоять в городе а нашим войскам
can't be stationed in our city
нельзя в нашем городе
now they just said about I wo
стоять сейчас только что сказали про
n't say Andryu don't look you say that
не скажу Андрю не смотри ты говоришь что
they bomb houses because our troops are
они бомбят дома потому что наши войска в
stationed in our cities yes But Russian troops
наших городах стоят да Но русские войска
in our cities in Kherson so in Bucha they
в наших городах в Херсоне так в буче
were in Borodyanka They were stationed  in the cities
были в бородянке Они стояли в городах
So how does it turn out that they didn't
Так это как получается так они не
cover civilians, they covered them
прикрывали же мирными жителями к они
in the cities,
тогда в городах
ours immediately start evacuating,
прикрывали наши сразу начинают эвакуацию
wait, from which Kherson were they evacuated,
подожди С какого Херсона эвакуировали
that people were evacuated from Kherson, your
Что людей из Херсона эвакуировали ваши
troops are in Kherson,
войска стоят в Херсоне
evacuation is impossible now, most likely
сейчас эвакуации невозможно скорее всего
because of your troops, Andryukh, what  ours
из-за ваших войск Андрюх каких наши
look This is awesome
смотри Это офигенная
in the world peace for the war not to be
ве миру мир за то чтобы войне не быть
look there will be no war this means that you
смотри войне не быть это значит что вы
should take God forbid that  we
должны забрать Дай Бог чтобы мы с тобой
met somewhere on not better better
где-нибудь увиделись на не лучше лучше
so that we don't come to us like that We
чтобы мы вот так не приезжайте к нам Мы
won't come to you and that's all
к вам не будем приезжать и всё
agreed domko fence from you big you
договорились домко забор от вас большой
know with electricity so that they
такой знаете с электричеством чтобы был
don't get
чтобы не лезли
in here you have nothing from the country  there will be no
сюда у вас-то от страны ничего не
slaves left in the end why
останется в о концовке рабам вас почему
and why Well Poland will take its own Lithuania its
а почему Ну Польша своё заберёт Литва
own Latvia its own We ours And who are we Look,
своё Латвия своё Мы своё А мы это кто
you Tatars, look, you don't have a state
Вот вы татары смотри у вас нет государ
ROSI we are Russia don't look, you are a Tatar, you are
РОСИ мы Россия не смотри ты татарин ты
under Russian occupation and that's where
под оккупацией российской и ты вот где
the work is
работа
we are the deputy  svo What is yours here What is yours here
мы зам сво А что тут твоё что тут твоё
Tatar in Ukraine everything that is Russian
татарское в Украине всё что российское
everything is mine I am Russian And that is, you are already
всё моё я россиянин А то есть ты уже
such a cosmopolitan imperialist without without a country
такой космополит имперец без без страны
without a Motherland yes it
без Родины да
turns out that my
получается вот моя
country is Russia I understand yes that is, you have
страна Россия я понял да то есть ты свои
already forgotten your roots You are nobody you  And do you at least
корни уже забыл Ты никто ты А ты хоть
know the Tatar language very well? Look, the letter is not lost yet.
знаешь очень смотри ещё не ВС потеряно
And look. And you say,
так и письмо Да и смотри И ты говоришь
we will take ours. We will take ours. So
вот мы заберём своё мы заберём своё Так
what's yours here?  in
а что тут твоего в
Ukraine
Украине
What what is your home Here people are brothers
Что что тебе родное Тут люди братья
What brothers to you all who are not spoiled are
Какие братья тебе все кто не испорчены
usually children that is look
это как правило дети то есть вот смотри
now people are sitting in Odessa for example like this or
сидят сейчас люди в Одессе напри так или
here and You tell them we will take you to
вот и Ты им говоришь мы вас заберём к
ourselves yes
себе да
Ma here you are you are a maniac  Because you
Ма вот ты ты и есть маньяк Потому что ты
want you sit in Tatarstan and you
хочешь ты сидишь в Татарстане и ты
want these lands with these people you know
хочешь эти земли с этими людьми знаешь
how Koschei is like I don't want anything and you
как Кощей такой не ничего не хочу причём
know what Look you have me look I
знаешь что Смотри ты у меня смотри я
know how the president laughs something
тебе знаешь как президент что-то хохочет
not That's it look you started you started with
не Во так смотри ты начал ты начал с
that I am cold that the prince is not there your
того что я холо что княз нет у тебя
eyes lit up We will return ours you do not
глаза засветились Мы вернём своё ты не
say it is the politicians there who want to take
говоришь это политики там хотят забрать
you away you are burning We will return ours you know in you
ты горишь Мы вернём своё знаешь у тебя
here a demon
вот демон
is waking up Andryukh for you until I
просыпается Андрюх тебе пока я
watch it again don't watch that is you see
пересмотрю не смотри то есть ты видишь
you are some kind of imperialist imperialist  And you
ты какой-то имперец имперец такой И вот
know what I noticed in Russian I suppose you
знаешь что я заметил в русски полагаю ты
want to edit something there so that
ещё там что-то смонтировать хочешь чтобы
later it won't be me I am without editing That is, this is
потом не я Я без монтажа То есть я вот
how I speak to people
так как с людьми говорю Смотри просто
Look, it just turns out that people from Lubino, Russian, they tell us that we want to take Russian from here, well, somehow it doesn’t fit in my head, what do you mean in this What was your town called there, Nabm, Balma, how many people are there in Gul? Well, officially 82, 82. Here. look in Gul 82000 population so province small go When you leave for the north then T 8199 so at this moment and what will be better for you in this ball if there Kherson Dnepr Kyiv Andryukh you hear me please Andryukh Andryukh right now a minute no matter how much you don't want me interrupt please Listen Look Andryukh I don't need anything personally I don't want anything I apologize paraphrasing I want brothers not to shoot each other so that mothers don't remain without sons so that children have fathers fathers here's how to tell you so that this doesn't happen so that this everything stopped That's what I want I don't want there who has land I have enough Look, I have an apartment in Sadgorod and that's enough for me  You understand, so that this does not
хватает Понимаешь вот этого чтобы не
happen But if it started, it started So it’s
было Но если это началось это началось
not just like that Look, a minute has
Значит не просто так вот смотри минута
not passed Yes, roughly speaking, 30 seconds
не прошла Да грубо говоря секунд 30
have passed
прошло
60% of the world’s resources
60% примерно мировых ресурсов вот с
are located in Russia from our little globe, I am all of
нашего шарика находится в России я вся
Europe Yes, the whole planet is licking its lips at
Европа Да вся планета облизывается на
Russia, it looks and  initially what are
Россию смотрит и изначально что ты вот
you surprised about, is it
ты удивлён разве вот мировых ресурсов
really true that
реально
60% of the world's resources are in Russia, Gas, Oil, there is ore, I don't know,
60% в России Газ Нефть там руда не знаю
Nickel, it's all the same, it's all the same,
Никель это всё одно это всё без этого
you can basically live without it, you can't live
можно в принципе прожить нельзя прожить
without it, the only source without
без вот единственный источник без
which you will really die is water,
которого ты реально сдохнешь - это вода
that is, the Volga
то есть Волга
Kama how big is our Yenisei
Кама как у нас большой этот Енисей
about no Yenisei
об нет Енисей
about the lake the lake is Big this is cool Baikal
об озеро озеро Большое это крутое Байкал
ka without this you really can't have you been
ка вот без этого реально нельзя ты был
to
на
Baikal once not once yes And look and now
Байкале раз ни разу да А смотри а теперь
you say 60% of the globe's resources are
ты говоришь 60% земного шарика ресурсов
in Russia and why are you then in  in such a
в России а почему ты же тогда в такой
resource-rich country you live worse than a
богатой ресурсами стране живёшь хуже чем
poor one
бедная
[laughter]
[смех]
Holland they have no gas, no oil, no forest
Голландию у них ни газа ни нефти ни леса
at all
вообще
they are just a stoned weed the
нету они тупо травки
emperor lives well And so what about the serfs  Well,
император Хорошо живёт Так а холопы Ну
somehow, in a small apartment there, but it's
как-то вот в маленькой квартирке там но
normal. We live Andryukh. If only there hadn't been a war.
нормально Живём Андрюх войны бы не было
Look. Well, you agree that you live
смотри Ну ты ты согласен что ты живёшь
worse than people in Europe. People in
хуже чем люди в Европе люди в Европе А
Europe. And you've been to Europe. You've been to
ты был в Европе ты был в
Europe. And for me, it's enough to look at the fact
Европе А мне достаточно вот смотреть то
that these  allow their
что эти позволяют своим
children same-sex children you were in Europe in the
детям однополых детей ты в Европе был в
countries of Europe
странах Европы
was knocked down to the knees adopt
был сбитый по колено усыновляют ещё
someone else they have there
кого-то у них там сй
specifically Russia in some
конкретно России в какой-то
country Besides Russia in some country
стране Кроме России в какой-то стране
was Not yet not Yeah That is you other
был Ещё не не Ага То есть ты других
countries not  I saw how people live there I didn't
стран не видел как там люди живут не
see and in Russia in which cities have you been
видел а в России в каких ты городах был
regions in which except Tatarstan and the
регионах в каких кроме Татарстана и
North Well which ones Andryukh well which ones for
Севера Ну каких уж Андрюх ну какие
example
например
in Moscow in St. Petersburg Oh so in Russia well the
ну в Москве в Питере О так по России ну
Northern lot
Северная участь
work that is look it turns out you you in
работа то есть смотри получается ты ты в
such
такой
in such a resource-rich country So
в такой богатой ресурсами стране Так
60% if there are 60% of the globe's resources and
60% если там 60% земного шара ресурсов и
they are mined, then it goes into someone's
их добывают значит кому-то это идёт в
pocket if not you then
карман если не тебе то
someone Well, how can anyone care about everything for the provision of
кому Ну как кому уж всё на обеспечение
tanks, missiles, aircraft That is, it
танков ракет самолётов То есть
turns out that the head of the
получается зава
VM is above So that who  -somewhere from behind  didn't
ВМ быть над Чтобы кто-нибудь сзади не
sneak up we have no right to drop the soap
подкрался не имеем права уронить мыло
Pony pony that's why we spend
Поня пони поэтому мы каждый раз тратим
on soap every time dropped We have but that is I
на мыло уронили У нас есть но то есть я
understood Look you have the richest country But
понял Смотри у вас богатейшая страна Но
you have to Everything in tanks in Airplanes Yes
вам Всё приходится в танки в Самолёты Да
use all
использовать все
the money of your
деньги свою
life Come on get out of here Yes
жизы Давай иди отсюда Да
wait Yes  what are you let's talk ok now
подожди Да что ты давай хоро сейчас
So let me already agree with the
поговорим Так давай я уже договорюсь с
guy
пацаном
Eduard so everything guy
эдуар так всё паца
m bro it's scary to swear there to be
м братан это стрёмно материться там
rude something it Everyone has Well I'm
грубить что-то это Каждый имеет Ну я
listening you wanted to express yourself You're
слушаю вы хоти хотели выразиться Ты же
not a Ukrainian at all to who
вро нет какой не украинец вообще к кто
vatka Tell me what  do you have a pain in your soul
вате Расскажите что у вас болит на душе
And what is it that hurts in your soul tell
А что у вас на душе болит расскажите у
me
меня
yes yes what is it that hurts in your soul
да да что у вас болит на душе
because you are on A I understood you are Napoleon
потому что вы на А я понял вы Наполеон
Yes yes
Да да я
who am I looking at that
кто я так смотрю что
you I am looking at that you are so a couple
Вы Я смотрю что Вы так парочка
I am those  and I say No What's your
я те и говорю Не Как вас
name Me Yes Gelu sak gay lyuk Yeah law
зовут Меня Да Гелю сак гей люк Ага закон
Gelu gay
Гелю гей
[music]
[музыка]
lyusa Okay guys then  I
люса Ладно пацаны тогда 15 минут дома
'll be home in 15 minutes 15 minutes Yes, run home Otherwise
буду 15 минут Да беги домой А то сейчас
he'll tell
он
you a
тебя а
e a
е а
nono minutes I'll be
ноно минут буду
home honestly in a
дома честно сечас
second Andryu Sorry please in
секунду Андрю Извини пожалуйста сейчас
a second you wanted to talk to m
секунду ты с м хотел поговорить
obva Man talk and some gay barges in
обва Челове поговорить и влазит какой-то
really interferes with
правда мешает
conversations
разговорам
ambassador you hate us  we respect you
послу ты нас ненавидишь мы вас уважаем
This is your right And this is our right I am
Вот это твоё право А это наше право я
now to argue, to dispute somehow and to
это сейчас спорить оспаривать как-то и
talk about power and about that
разговаривать зау власть и зау в том
May God give you health May God grant that this
Дай Бог тебе здоровь Дай Бог чтобы это
ends as quickly as possible And let's once
как можно быстрее закончилось И давай ещ
again to the past DM win Let's make this
раз прошедшим дм побе Давай чтобы это
faster
побыстрее
ended so that later from your salary
закончилось чтобы потом с твоей зарплаты
so in this Urengoy so to
так в этом Уренгое так
deduct deduct money for the
отчислить отчислять деньги на
restoration of Ukraine because
восстановление Украины потому что же
Russia will pay reparations She is
Россия будет выплачивать репарации Она
from what the princes make salaries and the
же это с чего зарплата князья делают а
serfs will pay
холопы будут выплачивать
the truth There we will
правда Там уж
figure it out the US weapons help them and
разберёмся США оружие им помогает и
will help to restore it is definitely not
восстановиться помогут однозначно не
indifferent  so it means that everything there is not the SBU until
безразлично же значит всё там не СБУ до
Victory, but ours because we must follow
Победы так наши потому что мы должны за
you Priti You must  still have to work out All
вами Прити Вы должны ещ отрабатывать Всё
Glory to Ukraine
Слава Украине
Come on Russia come on all
Давай Россия давай всего
the best Yes
доброго Да
awesomely told brothers Slavka chuvi
обалденно расска были братья Славка чуви
Toto here in the essence of the impe name
Тото вот во сутнисть импе имя
zaspituyuyutsya them on such zombies so
захоплюють их на таких зомба так
imperialists so from VN sit VN rose VN
имперцев так от ВН сидить ВН розу ВН
some kind of bang so VN to know yourself not to be
якийсь хлоп так ВН нать себе не
ashamed so to call and what am I  I'll make
соромиться так назвати а что я зроблю я
there a cotton there prince Ale VN infected there
там хлопа там князя Але ВН заражены там
we must return our anyway ku x
мы должны вернуть сво всё равно проку х
so Toto we Russia we
так Тото мы росия мы
INN itself seems Toto lki need Beti we will
ИНН сам каже Тото льки треба Бути
limit VN itself rose what is in them there VN
обмеженим ВН сам розу що в них там ВН
can Have
може Хав
60% resource earthly ku Ale many many
60% ресурс земно ку Але багато багато
resource  and VN won't think about why VN
ресурс и ВН нать не задумается чму ВН
lives in Bagh mu VN lives there's a kitchenette like this
живе в баг му ВН живе ця кухонька така
you know I don't know how small it is VN is
знаете не знаю якась маленька така ВН
bothering the kids  there on
мусить дити там на
work on that here and VH hoh
робит на ту при сюда и ВХ хох
Zhikh euro
Жих евро
live here zashchitaniye and in the beginning of the regatta I
жи тут заш питання и в начина регата я ж
I love such moments If you know to
я обожнюю так моменти Коли знаете до
Ludin to reach Ale von can not it
Людина доходить Але вона не може це
publicly say so Toto I think so
публично визнати так Тото Я думаю так
each one himself to make conclusions from this
кожен сам зробить висновок ще з цього
video write in comments what kind of
ролика напишить в коментарях яки
visnovki you did so from
висновки ви зробили так з
this Tatars Tatars so that they were
цього татары татары так тобто яки були
conquered by Moscow that there was a
завоёваны м московским что там было
kingdom or a principality so a princedom and
царство чи княжество так князивство и
that's what we have and what is the name of the program about
ось мы маем да Як имя пере програму о
these people here they are here to wonder
цих людей вот вони сюда дивляться
want to want to want to want some
захопити захопити захопити якась хвороба
kind of illness  mental write your thoughts and
така ментальна напишить свою думку и
write Tes on the channel tell your friends about the channel
пису Тесь на канал розказуй про канал
that we are leading information
друзям тому що ми ведем информаций
enlighten such for Slava  Ukrain writing on my
просвит таку дль Слава Укра пись на мий
Telegram right now axis VN and
Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН а
pok ce very and very important YouTube is busy
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That is why in order for
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
me Mali operational connections
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now  pok there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video still interesting and useful
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
constant operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukrai subscribe
YouTube Слава украи подпишись